<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Competior Analysis on Concho Resources</title>
    <link>/tags/competior-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Competior Analysis on Concho Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/competior-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Outside The Yellow: A Review of Leasing Activity Over the Last 12 Months</title>
      <link>/2018/04/12/outside-the-yellow-a-review-of-leasing-activity-over-the-last-12-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/12/outside-the-yellow-a-review-of-leasing-activity-over-the-last-12-months/</guid>
      <description>Data Sources and MethodologyDownloaded all lease activity for the prior twelve months using DrillingInfo.Joined leases level data to sections for mapping purposes.Identied trends in company leasing activity.Based on the previous twelve month time period in the Permian Basin, there are ~150,000 more records in the database compared to the DI landtrac system and is about a month ahead on filings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Parent/Child Well Development in New Mexico</title>
      <link>/2018/04/05/parent-child-wells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/04/05/parent-child-wells/</guid>
      <description>MethodologyCalculated horizontal distance to nearest wellbore using the midpoint of the lateral.Child wells were identified using three parameters:Distance Parameter: Horizontal distance less than or equal to 1,000’.Timing Parameter: Completion date greater than six months.Formation Parameter: Landing zone of parent well must be in the same zone as child well.Note: Also identified child wells regardless of formation to account for communication between zones (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limelight: A Closer Look at Diamondback&#39;s New Position</title>
      <link>/2018/02/19/limelight-a-closer-look-at-diamondback-s-new-position/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/19/limelight-a-closer-look-at-diamondback-s-new-position/</guid>
      <description>FocusDiamondback recently announced a new exploration play targeting the Mississippian oil play in Ector and Crane Counties.Company acquired ~19,000 acres which they plan on delineating beginning this year.The map below identifies offsetting permit/spud activity.Majority of activity is vertical development, with the most active operator, Oxy, North of their acreage.Adventure Operating has completed 2 horizontal wells on their acreage in 2016 and 2017 targeting the San Andreas formation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Pad Development Activity</title>
      <link>/2018/01/08/mapping-pad-development-activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/08/mapping-pad-development-activity/</guid>
      <description>Data Sources and MethodologyData obtained from IHS and filtered to permit dates beginning in 2017.Well cluster counts will identify pads, sections and multi-section development dependent upon well density.2nd map results were filtered by spud date to show activity starting in Q3’17. Map Identifies Developments From Permits, Spuds and Completions Beginning in 2017{&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>